I have been making these game guides for a decade now, but most have [been] removed for copyright [infringement]
or hate speech (fucking normies)
So I thought I'd react load a classic from 2006 with [the] music [redone] and half the video deleted
While everyone is talking about the avian flu. I want to talk about something that actually matters Runescape (obv)
It's one of the most popular games in the world, but why? (im asking for real)
Because it's free to play (*COUGH* WoW *COUGH*) a lot of us would rather be playing world of warcraft right now
But can't afford it or our computers are too weak (or both)
xx
512 megabytes of Ram [that's] Science fiction
BANG BANG KRACK
Now you might be recognizing things that aren't supposed to be in the game yet
That's not because the video is historically inaccurate [that's] because my dad created
Runescape and if you question it he will ban you
The point of this guide is to teach you how to get 99 in one skill
I wanted to do every skill, but that might take longer than the afternoon
I have I have [decided] to go [with] strength because it's the most common to have
99 in but I also want to see my room scape character become a rift
I'll also do the facts so I can use nice swords, so people don't call me mean names
Because it's 2006 and no one is standing [after] cyber bullying
First thing you want to do is grab your bronze sword and kill some poor Farmers Livelihood
You don't have to feel bad about it because it's the middle ages and they aren't going to live past 40
next you won't kill some giant rats and
Fuck free-to-Play. This is awful. [I] know where my mom keeps her credit card
So I bought membership as a member you can do a [queston] [skip] a lot of levels
[it's] called the waterfall quest and doing it feels like shooing on glass yeah level 31
Wait, you can get to level 31 from doing that quest then what's the point of a guide?
Just do that two and a half more times
And you're already at 99 so I'm going to switch skill to get 99 Defense
Higher depends [lets] you wear better or more which makes no sense first
It's bronze than iron steel then it's black
Black Metal
Norwegian armor no, thank you
I'm switching [to] prayer skill you bury bones
and the runescape gods gives you powers because you honored your kills by ripping off the flesh and
Buried the only part that can't decompose
I'm going to buy bones does that mean I'm
Honoring someone else's [kills] or am I committing sacrilege?
[I] don't know how to deal with harrassing Runescape, but I'm guessing it includes metal rods
So it's not worth [the] risk [not] Gonna get mined in an artery because fuck legolas. Yeah, that's right
I hated him before the Hobbit movies
[I] wanted to train Magic, but my runescape friend was supposed to get the runes hasn't logged in in forever
Where are you [Saddam] 37 last week? I was streaming through [realplayer]
I asked him what he was doing [ten] minutes after he responded he was gone
But this gives us an opportunity to get 99 in Runecrafting
The guide says travel to the continent of Saya and do a mini quest for ruin crafting Xp
Saya is not in the game yet, but don't worry. It's going to be released in a decade
They say it was decided in a business meeting, but that's obviously a lie
British companies don't have meetings business is discussed through panel shows taking a decade is just them being lazy
Getting to saya was an amazing adventure [the] mini quest is get a book for this guy shouldn't be that hard. [oh]
God finally it took like
48 minutes for Xp. I get [4] Xp
I have traveled the entire world Peter Jackson could have turned that into one movie fuck runecrafting
The next kill is construction player housing [I] searched everywhere for a good construction guide
But all of them just said get that money this one didn't even finish itself so I looked for a money making guide
But they all took time and effort, so I just pretended [to] be a bank burnt meat you idiot
I'm not a bank. This is some stuff. I was gonna bank with you. Oh
This is my house. I like it. I hope you do too because [this] is all I could afford. I am completely broke
Next health level you get to hit point Xp when you deal damage
I don't know if that works in real life because I have never killed anyone with a sword or a bow sadly
I can't train this one because I need money for food
Coins are serious business [though] it would be cool to make real money from online video
I heard the red [versus] blue guys made so much money
They could buy two ipods next skill is agility
It's like strength except you can brag about your healthy lifestyle to train agility. You need to do the known training course
This is fun, but what's the point of training if people don't know I'm training time to take some pictures from Myspace
Then [gnome] kingdom threw me out the [next] kill is [herb-lore]. It's where you take
Plants and turn them into well, this is a children's game
So they have to call it potions to train [herber]
We need to do a quest this guy wants us to Gather raw beef sure raw rat meat a bit weird, but okay
chicken and bear
Bear I'm not fighting a 500 kilo death machine for your stew
It's leaving time to level up thieving you need to pickpocket
why you can just kill people and take anything from their pockets when you reach a certain level you can steal from Stalls and
ruin Another person's Livelihood
Eventually when you hit a high enough level you can perform a heist the world [national] [bank] is the safest bank in the world
But some hard will be for us to take
everything
Very hard not doing it next [is] crafting [actually] know how to get 99 so this would be easy first you want to oh
I'm already level 5. I guess. I screwed up. Sorry guys
Fletching is one where you make bows and bow strings
Yes for some reason that needed to be a separate skill you put feathers on Stakes and level six
But a lot of money again, so what now a lot of billionaires in real life or hedge fund managers?
So I decided to start my own hedge fund but ten seconds of the starting it. I remember that
I don't really know what a hedge fund is but bankers listen
I found another way to make money that could work in real life everyone wants a player house, but it's expensive
So why not give literally everyone a housing loan? I mean everyone pays off their housing loans, so what could possibly [go] wrong?
Also, I'm giving up on fletching because I don't like what it has turned me into Slayer is the next skill
I still don't know what that is but to [train] it. I need to kill 15 [ice] fins
So slayer is world of Warcraft quests
So why even play Runescape when I could be playing neopets time to get 99 [Hunter]?
[I] can't train that I'm an animal rights activist. I'm going to have to do the opposite
I'm going to stop someone from getting 99 [Hunter], so I walked up this guy and said stop [it]
You don't have [to] kill virtual animals you can go out in the real world and make something of yourself
[and] he said you're right time to achieve my dreams, but I'm stuck with this dead-end government job
Do you really think we can shape our destiny like that? I said yes, we can
Yes, we can
I like it. I'm going to use it as my slogan. [I] said no he can't it's mine
I'll sue you and he logged out never caught his name, but his username was xxxx crazy Kenyan
The last Row is a bunch of free-to-play skills for you casuals with responsible parents first is mining
I want to explain what this skill is but it's just too damn complex
This is this is actually very relaxing is this the one [is] this where I get 99?
Next kill is smithing. We take our mind Oars and walk to Edge field
it's called that because everyone there is Edgy you see that next Edge feel that is the Wilderness the
PVp, so I think it's scary, so I'm going to ask my dad to remove it now [there] bronze [bars]
I am going to craft access because I will need them when I find a silly excuse to give up on this skill
For example, you can't Smith black metal
I for one am outraged and I am going to take a stand for
Norway next skill is fishing when you start out with fishing you can only fish shrimp
But don't worry there are a lot of things you can do with shrimp for example cook shrimp
And that's it apparently Bubba lied to us next ah cooking another skill. I have already failed
[I] got those levels when I am today a developer cook-off
I came in fourth with a delicious tenderloin steak and the guy who won microwaved the frozen pizza fucking nerds
Fire-making skills. Yes, that is a skill don't mock it setting fire to logs is considered these chests of the forest
But how on Earth do you get logs?
There's one over there of course they spawn randomly just like in real life [after] [going] on a log adventure
I am ready to set fire to them now. This was exciting never doing it again
Wood cutting skill, but how on Earth do you find trees?
I'll guess [I] just shot down these trees on this private property. [I'm] sure they won't mind
They [mined] and now I don't have an axe the next skill is
Farming that's literally all I did in the last video. So [what] do I do now?
and
That day for no particular reason
I decided to go [for] a little run so I ran to the end of the road
Then I thought maybe I'll run to the end of town then I thought why [not] run all the way to my rock then I
Ran out of energy so I logged out so maybe I didn't get level 99 in any scale
But didn't I get level 99 in friendship, and that is to kill an experienced?